<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HideShowToolbarFAB</string>
    <string name="long_random_text">
        Depart do be so he enough talent. Sociable formerly six but handsome. Up do view time they shot. He concluded disposing provision by questions as situation. Its estimating are motionless day sentiments end. Calling an imagine at forbade. At name no an what like spot. Pressed my by do affixed he studied.

        He unaffected sympathize discovered at no am conviction principles. Girl ham very how yet hill four show. Meet lain on he only size. Branched learning so subjects mistress do appetite jennings be in. Esteems up lasting no village morning do offices. Settled wishing ability musical may another set age. Diminution my apartments he attachment is entreaties announcing estimating. And total least her two whose great has which. Neat pain form eat sent sex good week. Led instrument sentiments she simplicity.

        Arrived compass prepare an on as. Reasonable particular on my it in sympathize. Size now easy eat hand how. Unwilling he departure elsewhere dejection at. Heart large seems may purse means few blind. Exquisite newspaper attending on certainty oh suspicion of. He less do quit evil is. Add matter family active mutual put wishes happen.

        Surprise steepest recurred landlord mr wandered amounted of. Continuing devonshire but considered its. Rose past oh shew roof is song neat. Do depend better praise do friend garden an wonder to. Intention age nay otherwise but breakfast. Around garden beyond to extent by.

        And sir dare view but over man. So at within mr to simple assure. Mr disposing continued it offending arranging in we. Extremity as if breakfast agreement. Off now mistress provided out horrible opinions. Prevailed mr tolerably discourse assurance estimable applauded to so. Him everything melancholy uncommonly but solicitude inhabiting projection off. Connection stimulated estimating excellence an to impression.

        Allow miles wound place the leave had. To sitting subject no improve studied limited. Ye indulgence unreserved connection alteration appearance my an astonished. Up as seen sent make he they of. Her raising and himself pasture believe females. Fancy she stuff after aware merit small his. Charmed esteems luckily age out.

        Still court no small think death so an wrote. Incommode necessary no it behaviour convinced distrusts an unfeeling he. Could death since do we hoped is in. Exquisite no my attention extensive. The determine conveying moonlight age. Avoid for see marry sorry child. Sitting so totally forbade hundred to.

        Oh acceptance apartments up sympathize astonished delightful. Waiting him new lasting towards. Continuing melancholy especially so to. Me unpleasing impossible in attachment announcing so astonished. What ask leaf may nor upon door. Tended remain my do stairs. Oh smiling amiable am so visited cordial in offices hearted.

        Preserved defective offending he daughters on or. Rejoiced prospect yet material servants out answered men admitted. Sportsmen certainty prevailed suspected am as. Add stairs admire all answer the nearer yet length. Advantages prosperous remarkably my inhabiting so reasonably be if. Too any appearance announcing impossible one. Out mrs means heart ham tears shall power every.

        Good draw knew bred ham busy his hour. Ask agreed answer rather joy nature admire wisdom. Moonlight age depending bed led therefore sometimes preserved exquisite she. An fail up so shot leaf wise in. Minuter highest his arrived for put and. Hopes lived by rooms oh in no death house. Contented direction september but end led excellent ourselves may. Ferrars few arrival his offered not charmed you. Offered anxious respect or he. On three thing chief years in money arise of.
    </string>
</resources>
